Chastity Duhaney

Software Engineer Atlanta, GA| (678-548-0917)

SUMMARY

Being in the Healthcare Industry for over 15 years helped prepare me to be an amazing intern/entry level software developer by teaching me to exhibit strong communication and problem-solving skills with clients as well as co-workers. It also taught me how to exemplify excellent customer relationship skills by being able to adapt and learn quickly in any situation.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

♦ HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, ES6, React, Redux, Python, Java, Bootstrap, Node.js, PostgreSQL, AWS, PM2, GitHub, Express.js, Node.js

EDUCATION

DigitalCrafts | Pursing Certificate in Software Engineering- Atlanta, GA Feb 2019-May 2019

♦ Software engineering training program covering a full-stack development including, but not limited to JavaScript, Python, including an emphasis on cutting-edge frameworks like React/Redux and server-side technologies including Node.js, Express, and PostgreSQL.

Clayton State University | B.S. in Psychology & Human Services

December 2010

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT PORTFOLIO

DoTheThing | <u>dothething.chastityduhaney.com</u>

March 2019

- ♦ Member of a group of 3 that formed a ticketing system application that works across most screen and web-browsers
- Created full-stack app that used Linux to deploy the application in AWS
- ♦ Used PostgreSQL to create the data base

Movie.io | movie.io.rebeccauranga.com

March 2019

- ♦ Member of a group of 3 that formed front-end web application using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Implemented 2 remote APIs to pull in the data for the project
- ♦ Learned and implemented bootstrap as part of the design

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Delta Airlines Inc.

GA

Logistician
(October 2017-

October 2018)

- Continuously improved processes for warehousing and distribution of aircraft parts
- Prioritized and managed multiple tasks as it pertains to departmental needs

Northside Hospital Patient Access Rep Atlanta, GA (May 2016-December 2017)

- Upheld all hospital policies and Federal & State guidelines as it pertained to patient's information.
- Analyzed patient's insurance coverage by appropriately conducting insurance eligibility search, reducing the incidence of claim denial.

Eye Consultants of Atlanta <u>CSC</u>

Atlanta, GA (Feb 2015-July 2015)

- Scheduled appropriate appointments for patients according to schedule guidelines.
- Ensured proper inputting of patients' information in a timely and efficient manner as pertains to policy and procedures